Guide to the Howard Brubaker Papers MSS.053
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Magazines, Newspapers and Miscellaneous Periodicals
  - The Red Cross Magazine; August, 1919; October, 1919; February, 1920; April, 1920, 1919-1920 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Clippings from Success Magazine, "Pulse of the World" Section; Jan., Feb., Mar., Apr. 1911 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Clipping from La Follette's (date unknown), p. 6, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Clipping from Child Life, August 1932 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Clipping from The Literary Digest, January 16, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The New Republic; Feb. 20, Mar. 5, Mar. 26, Apr. 23, Jun. 4, Jul. 2, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The New Republic; Jul. 23, Aug. 13, Sept. 3, Oct. 1, Oct. 8, Oct. 15, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - The New Republic; Oct. 22, Oct. 29, Nov. 19, Dec. 17, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - The New Republic; Jan. 7, Jan. 28, Mar. 18, Apr. 1, Apr. 22, Jun. 3, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - The New Republic; May 5, Jun. 9, Oct. 20, Nov. 3, Nov. 17, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - The New Republic; Jan. 4, Feb. 15, Jul. 18, Oct. 24, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - The New Republic; May 29, Jul. 31, 1929; Mar. 19, Nov. 26, 1930; Sept. 16, Nov. 4, 1931, 1929-1931 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The New Republic; Apr. 27, Jun. 29, Jul. 13, Aug. 31, Oct. 26, Nov. 9, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - The New Republic, Dec. 6, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - The National Post; May 20, Jun. 3, Jun. 17, Jul. 1, 1911; Feb. 1931 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Bulletin of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, February 1931 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Opera House Program, 1911-1912 Season (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Opera Libretti: La Traviata, Lohengrin, Punchinello, Les Contes d'Hoffmann, Girl of the Golden West, La Favorita, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Opera Libretti: Les Huguenots, Rigoletto, Cavalleria Rusticana, Siegfried, Tristan und Isolde, Manon, L'Aiglon, As You Like It, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous political and culinary pamphlets not by Brubaker, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Series III: Correspondence
  - Brubaker to his wife, undated (Box III:1, Folder 1)
  - Early papers (1920-1922) (Box III:1, Folder 2)
  - Personal letters: B - D, undated (Box III:1, Folder 3)
  - Personal letters: E - J, undated (Box III:1, Folder 4)
  - Personal letters: K - R, undated (Box III:1, Folder 5)
  - Personal letters: S - Z, undated (Box III:1, Folder 6)
  - Early fan mail (1915-1925) (Box III:1, Folder 7)
  - Fan mail - Harpers and other periodicals, undated (Box III:1, Folder 8)
  - Fan mail - The New Yorker, undated (Box III:1, Folder 9)
  - Fan mail - The New Yorker, undated (Box III:1, Folder 10)
  - Fan mail, paragraph suggestions from correspondents, and soliciations, undated (Box III:1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with literary agents: Brandt & Brandt, undated (Box III:1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with literary agents: Brandt & Brandt, undated (Box III:1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with literary agents: Brandt & Brandt, undated (Box III:1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with literary agents: Brandt & Brandt, undated (Box III:1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence with publishers: Vanguard Press, undated (Box III:1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with publishers: The New Republic, undated (Box III:1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence with publishers: Harold Ross; The New Yorker, undated (Box III:1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with publishers: The New Yorker, undated (Box III:1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with publishers: Harper & Brothers (Thomas Wells), undated (Box III:1, Folder 20)
  - Writer's Publishing Co. - Notes, letters, and memos, undated (Box III:1, Folder 21)
- Series IV: Financial Records
  - Bills, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 1)
  - Bills, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Maurice Brubaker, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 3)
  - Income tax returns, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 4)
  - Tax records, insurance, correspondence from creditors, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 5)
  - Invoices: A - B, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 6)
  - Invoices: C - H, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 7)
  - Invoices: I - N, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 8)
  - Invoices: O - Z, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box IV:1, Folder 10)
- Series V: Unsorted Newspaper Clippings
  - Original clippings and photocopies., undated (Box V:1, Folder data_value_missing_eca26c5a8ee427542d04f358dea08218)
  - Original clippings., undated (Box V:2, Folder data_value_missing_7ceab0214722bd0dd1ee856136bde091)
- Series VI: Oversize Material
  - Contains Brubaker head shots, a leather billfold, galleys, and an advertisement for Brubaker's column in The Daily Mirror., undated (Box VI:1, Folder data_value_missing_bf9a0ec7717f207a4dc9f36f3f3036a2)